NARRATOR:
Previously on The Big Bang Theory:
I'm going to the Arctic Circle with
Leonard, Wolowitz and Koothrappali.
-For three months?
-Yes.
What did you mean when you said
you were going to miss me?
[SIGHS]
It means I wish you weren't going.
(Leonard:)Oh, thank God we're home.
(Howard:)I can't believe we spent three months
in that frozen hell.
(Raj:)It was like a snowy nightmare
from which there was no awakening.
(Sheldon:)I don't know what Arctic expedition
you were on...
(Sheldon:)...I thought it was a hoot and a half.
(Sheldon:)Oh, hi, Mom.
(Sheldon:)No. I told you I'd call you when I got home.
I'm not home yet.
All right. I'm home.
(Sheldon:)The Arctic expedition
was a remarkable success.